# **Ayush Kumar Singh**

# **UI/Frontend Engineer**

ayush.singh.xda@gmail.com • +91 7011 439 788 • Noida, India • www.ayushsingh.net

# **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

I am a professional **UI/UX Designer** and **Front end developer**. I like to take responsibility for crafting end to end User Experience from prototyping to develop the actual product. I help to craft **great user experiences** using **modern frontend architecture**.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **UX ENGINEER**

DLT Labs Private Limited, Noida

December 2019 - PRESENT

# **UX ENGINEER (Freelance)**

SOE Technologies Pvt. Ltd, Noida

July 2020 - PRESENT

#### **UX ENGINEER**

SOE Technologies Pvt. Ltd, Noida

July 2019 - November 2019

# **SKILLS**

- Javascript
- Angular
- HTML/CSS
- Git SCM
- Web Animations (GSAP/SVG)

**TOOLS** 

Figma, Sketch

Adobe Creative Suite

- UI/UX Design
- Responsive Web Design

# **CO-CURRICULAR**

UI/UX Designer, Frontend Developer

Software Incubator, AKGEC

September 2016 - May 2019

### **PROJECTS**

Professional projects & Side projects are viewable at: www.ayushsingh.net

# **EDUCATION**

B.Tech - Information Technology

AJAY KUMAR GARG ENGINEERING COLLEGE, (AKTU)

2015-2019

**Elementary Education** 

DMA, Meerut (CBSE)

2004-2014

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Lead Student coordinator, SDC-SI, 2018-2019
- HTML / CSS Mentor at Workshop, SDC-SI, AKGEC, 2018
- 1st position at Web Design hackathon, IMSUC, 2017
- SVG Mentor at Workshop, SDC-SI, AKGEC, 2017
- 1st position in Web and Graphic Design hackathon, ABES ACM 2017
- 1st position at Web Design hackathon, IMSUC, 2016
- Lead Designer at AKGEC College Fest, 2016
- Recognized Themer at xda-developers.com, 2014